### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/stephenlow (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Advertising
Online Advertising
Publishing

### Languages

Chinese

Malay

Mandarin

**English** 

### **Publications**

A FINE ART
PHOTOJOURNALISTIC
APPROACH TO WEDDING
PHOTOGRAPHY

# Stephen L.

Key Account Director at JETMIND Selangor

# Summary

Stephen has over 17 years of experience in digital world working with medium to big size brands. He is adept at managing creative solutions across varied marketing communication platforms.

His motto from the beginning has always been this: be the solution provider for client and be the extension of their marketing team.

His goal is to deliver direct impact value to whatever task he is engaged in and getting the job done. A passionate and driven individual with extensive business knowledge, combined with a proven track record of revenue growth and performance improvement.

Highly organised and agile, Stephen is a hands-on multi-tasker with a strategic integrated mindset and exceptional work ethic.

I am a driven go-getter specializing in social-media, on-line & off-line marketing. I have a keen understanding different segments and on-lines audiences and have a proven track record of successful strategies and campaigns for my clients.

My ambition is to be the best trusted partner for my existing and potential clients in all matters of on-line presence and on-line marketing strategies. My commitment is to build my clients on-line brand equity with the best value-proposition.

# Experience

JETMIND
Key Account Director
January 2021 - Present (1 year)
Federal Territory of Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Value Online Sdn Bhd Digital Marketing Manager April 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 9 months) Malaysia

Value Online sdn bhd is a startup company, core business was a warehouse storage with 28,000 sqft located at puchong. With the EWMS software that integrated with selluseller.com as im taking part to understand the entire flow for from logistic inbound/outbound work process. In my position was require to build a new brand call fabbo.com.

Fabbo.com is a eCommerce store cater for health & beauty product. My role was build the entire brand from Logo design, namecard, social media page and management, campaign for 11.11 & 12.12 etc, setup facebook live streaming, entire eCommerce website by using shopify plus and placement ads google shopping.

To lead the marketing team for coordinating and executing strategies to acquire, convert and retain customers through FABBO.my with digital marketing strategy.

Eduspec Holdings Berhad Online Community Manager January 2015 - February 2018 (3 years 2 months) Shah Alam, Malaysia

- Manage existing social media channels and create new channels.
- Engage with target audiences around-the-clock by sharing content, finding ways to grow engagement with customers and industry influencers, and improve overall engagement.
- Monitor and respond to prospects/clients community posts as needed.
- Create, manage and maintain marketing content used for blogs, social media and communities.
- Manage the layout, scheduling and publishing of internally generated blog posts.
- · Report on KPIs and suggest new strategies for improvement.

Luxburando Social Media Manager January 2014 - December 2014 (1 year) Petaling Jaya

#### **Professional Summary**

- Develop new business, maintain and services the current or existing client.
- Provide training, develop and accompany subordinate on field.
- Support Back end team on client servicing, follow up on report and lead to sales director.
- Strategic business directions responsibility.
- Managed team size of 10.
- Strategic Digital Website development and marketing
- To identify areas of improvement for better results

Overall responsibilities include leading a digital team in Malaysia to manage online advertising, social media marketing, SEO/SEM, digital campaigns, event, print media, magazine and partnerships - to strengthen and increase awareness of the TOP10around.com, increase and drive online conversion, and help the company sustain its strong track record of growth.

Flame Production
Professional Portrait Photography
January 2008 - December 2013 (6 years)
Damansara

Over the pass 5 years been traveled more than 20 cities around the world for destination wedding portrait photography to plan to develop to multiple client with different variety of industry.

Portfolios managed ranging from travel to Luxury Apparels, Insurance Company, F&B, Mobile web development.

Passionate in pushing boundaries among more 'conservative' or clients who are comfortable in their 'safe-zone' to expand or increase their brand exposure and consumer experience to build a closer gap or missing link between the brand and their consumers. Enthusiastic in driving creative channel innovation.

Continuous and 'relentness' effort in cultivating, nurturing and mentoring the new and next generation of passionate communication planners.

My ambition is to be the best trusted partner for my existing and potential clients in all matters of presence and marketing strategies.

My commitment is to build my clients brand equity with the best valueproposition.

### **NPG AGENCY**

Digital Media Manager January 2013 - October 2013 (10 months)

Wisma Peter

#### Main responsibilities:

- Social Media Marketing & Online Public Relations
- Online PPC Advertising (Facebook, Google, YouTube)
- Strategy & Implementation: Lead Generation, Capture & Nurture using Lead Magnets
- · Management, Development and Strategy
- · Capturing and Editing Development of Photo & Video content
- Wordpress Administration
- · Technical Support

Centinnial Elite Agency
Digital Media Manager
January 2012 - December 2012 (1 year)
Puchong

- · Online Marketing
- · Social Media Marketing
- Facebook Marketing Campaign & Contest
- Search Engine Marketing (SEO)
- · Email Marketing
- Display Advertising

### Offline Marketing (Traditional Marketing)

- Marketing campaign
- Road Shows
- Event Management
- · Product launches

Asia City Media Group Advertising Sales Manager January 2009 - December 2011 (3 years) Industrial Guide Asia Assistant Sales Manager January 2006 - December 2008 (3 years) Puchong

Nanyang Press Marketing Sdn Bhd Senior Sales Representative June 2005 - December 2005 (7 months) Petaling Jaya

PanPages Berhad Advertising Sales Executive January 2004 - May 2005 (1 year 5 months) Bandar Sunway

Orange Media Group, Inc. Advertising Executive June 2003 - December 2003 (7 months) Puchong

Cyber Village Sdn Bhd Web Design Consultant June 2001 - May 2003 (2 years) Mont kiara

HVD Entertainment Sdn Bhd Web Designer June 1999 - May 2001 (2 years) Cheras

## Education

Saito Academy
Diploma, Advertising & Photography